希望黎明能早点到来
Say the dawn is drawing near
告诉我：「太阳很快就会出现」
Tell me that the sun will soon appear
阳光闪耀，宛如黄金
Beam of light, or ray of gold
黄色布满了每个角落
Yellow passing all around the world
两眼开开的你不会懂
You don't know until you've seen it blind
少了希望还有什么用
It won't show if all your faith has died
艳丽的太阳
Luz del sol (Light of Sun)
明亮的月亮
Destello de la Luna (Gleam of the Moon)
余光已悄悄离去
Aftershine has come and gone
我们还以为，太阳仍在天上
Some of us still feel it's going on
离别会有谁不懂
Separate everybody knows
但两眼阖上，谁看得出区别
But there's no difference if your eyes are closed
我们总是能找到出路
Somehow we all find our way around
突然我们就这样迷路
Now and then we're nowhere to be found
艳丽的太阳
Luz del sol (Light of Sun)
明亮的月亮
Destello de la Luna (Gleam of the Moon)
艳丽的太阳
Luz del sol (Light of Sun)
明亮的月亮
Destello de la Luna (Gleam of the Moon)